Jeremiah Krakowski: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Hello.
Jeremiah Krakowski: See, Dorothy's on here.
Dorothy: Hello!
Jeremiah Krakowski: Let's see… I'm on my phone right now, my main computer is…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Coming up here, it was 7th.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Open up Zoom here on this…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Yeah, we're gonna switch zoom over here.
Jeremiah Krakowski: So today is our live Q&A.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Today… There we go, now we're back on my…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Computer. Okay, let me go into the…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Group, and let's go live in the group.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Live.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Q&A… Review day…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Video…
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Go live.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Set it up to go live…
Jeremiah Krakowski: How you doing, Dorothy?
Jeremiah Krakowski: How've you been?
Jeremiah Krakowski: Stream key…
Dorothy: Aye.
Jeremiah Krakowski: New custom stream key…
Dorothy: I'm on my computer, which sometimes freezes.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Dorothy, how you been?
Dorothy: I'm good, I'm good. Yeah, I've been very busy running the yoga membership, which…
Jeremiah Krakowski: Can't hear ya.
Dorothy: Oh, right.
Dorothy: Can you hear me now?
Dorothy: Hello? Can you hear me?
Dorothy: Hello?
Dorothy: Hello? Can you hear me, Jeremiah?
Jeremiah Krakowski: You're still muted, Dorothy.
Dorothy: Oh, alright, I don't know why.
Jeremiah Krakowski: I've got the mute off, it's… Oh, no, you're not muted, let me see, my… my… my audio is wrong.
Jeremiah Krakowski: There we go, I can hear you now.
Dorothy: Right.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Wrong audio there.
Jeremiah Krakowski: Alright.
Dorothy: So…